captcha.com 2014-06-25

# captcha.com Privacy Policy | captcha.com

We are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and e-mail).

That is why Captcha, Inc has established this privacy policy, so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. Customers are very important to us and we want to know who you are, but not abuse the information you give us.

Most of the captcha.com web site can be visited without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles: 

## Choice

There are times when we collect personal information from you. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. You will have the option to "opt out" of certain uses of the information.

If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the captcha.com Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services. 

## Accuracy

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us. 

## Commitment

We are committed to privacy and will only use the information you provide us as you request. Mistakes are possible; miscommunication is possible. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [**webmaster@captcha.com**](mailto:webmaster@captcha.com). We will address any issue to the best of our abilities. 

Thank you for your support of these policies and of Captcha, Inc. 

### Subscribe

  * BotDetect™ CAPTCHA New Version Releases ([RSS](http://captcha.com/feeds/botdetect_captcha_release_notes.rss "Subscribe to the BotDetect CAPTCHA New Version Releases RSS Feed"), [Atom](http://captcha.com/feeds/botdetect_captcha_release_notes.atom "Subscribe to the BotDetect CAPTCHA New Version Releases Atom Feed"))
